
{
    "courses": [
        {
            "courseId": "111",
            "title": "Signals & Systems",
            "description": "",
            "instructorId": "7777",
            "status": "APPROVED",
            "lessons": [
                {
                    "lessonID": "1",
                    "title": "Intro to Signals",
                    "content": "signals classiffications",
                    "resources": [
                    ],
                    "quiz": {
                        "questions": [
                            {
                                "questionText": "All periodic signals are ...... siganls",
                                "options": [
                                    "Power",
                                    "Energy",
                                    "Neither",
                                    "More Info Needed"
                                ],
                                "correctAnswerIndex": 3
                            },
                            {
                                "questionText": "What are aperiodic signals ?",
                                "options": [
                                    "Non-periodic",
                                    "periodic",
                                    "Periodic but discrete",
                                    "Periodic but Analogue"
                                ],
                                "correctAnswerIndex": 0
                            }
                        ]
                    }
                },
                {
                    "lessonID": "2",
                    "title": "Unit Step",
                    "content": "u(t) function",
                    "resources": [
                    ],
                    "quiz": {
                        "questions": [
                            {
                                "questionText": "u(t) * u(t)",
                                "options": [
                                    "t",
                                    "t^2",
                                    "u(t)",
                                    "t u(t)"
                                ],
                                "correctAnswerIndex": 3
                            },
                            {
                                "questionText": "t u(t) equals to ...",
                                "options": [
                                    "t",
                                    "r(t)",
                                    "u(t).u(t)",
                                    "d(t)"
                                ],
                                "correctAnswerIndex": 1
                            }
                        ]
                    }
                },
                {
                    "lessonID": "3",
                    "title": "LEC-3",
                    "content": "Systems",
                    "resources": [
                    ],
                    "quiz": {
                        "questions": [
                            {
                                "questionText": "choose",
                                "options": [
                                    "wrong",
                                    "false",
                                    "true",
                                    "correct"
                                ],
                                "correctAnswerIndex": 3
                            },
                            {
                                "questionText": "choose 2.0",
                                "options": [
                                    "correct",
                                    "false",
                                    "true",
                                    "wrong"
                                ],
                                "correctAnswerIndex": 0
                            }
                        ]
                    }
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "courseId": "112",
            "title": "Technical Writing ",
            "description": "",
            "instructorId": "7777",
            "status": "APPROVED",
            "lessons": [
                {
                    "lessonID": "1",
                    "title": "Intro to T.W",
                    "content": "Abstraction Ladder",
                    "resources": [
                    ],
                    "quiz": {
                        "questions": [
                            {
                                "questionText": "Plagarism is....",
                                "options": [
                                    "presenting someone else's work, ideas, or words as your own without giving proper credit to the original source",
                                    "wrong answer",
                                    "correct answer",
                                    "IDK"
                                ],
                                "correctAnswerIndex": 0
                            },
                            {
                                "questionText": "Course Name is...",
                                "options": [
                                    "Critical writing",
                                    "Technical Writing",
                                    "T.W",
                                    "AY 7AGA"
                                ],
                                "correctAnswerIndex": 1
                            }
                        ]
                    }
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "courseId": "113",
            "title": "Critical Thinking",
            "description": "Thinking Critically",
            "instructorId": "7777",
            "status": "APPROVED",
            "lessons": [
                {
                    "lessonID": "1",
                    "title": "LEC-0",
                    "content": "INtro",
                    "resources": [
                    ],
                    "quiz": {
                        "questions": [
                            {
                                "questionText": "choose",
                                "options": [
                                    "correct",
                                    "answer",
                                    "solution",
                                    "TRUE"
                                ],
                                "correctAnswerIndex": 0
                            },
                            {
                                "questionText": "Choose 2.0",
                                "options": [
                                    "False",
                                    "True",
                                    "Correct",
                                    "Answer"
                                ],
                                "correctAnswerIndex": 2
                            }
                        ]
                    }
                },
                {
                    "lessonID": "2",
                    "title": "LEC-1",
                    "content": "lecture2",
                    "resources": [
                    ],
                    "quiz": {
                        "questions": [
                            {
                                "questionText": "choose correct answer",
                                "options": [
                                    "Correct answer",
                                    "wrong answer",
                                    "correct",
                                    "answer"
                                ],
                                "correctAnswerIndex": 0
                            },
                            {
                                "questionText": "Choose Correct Answer",
                                "options": [
                                    "Corrcet Answer",
                                    "Correct",
                                    "Answer",
                                    "Correct Answer"
                                ],
                                "correctAnswerIndex": 3
                            },
                            {
                                "questionText": "Choose Correct Answer",
                                "options": [
                                    "yes",
                                    "no",
                                    "true",
                                    "Neither"
                                ],
                                "correctAnswerIndex": 3
                            }
                        ]
                    }
                },
                {
                    "lessonID": "3",
                    "title": "LEC-2",
                    "content": "lecture-2",
                    "resources": [
                    ],
                    "quiz": {
                        "questions": [
                            {
                                "questionText": "Choose False Option",
                                "options": [
                                    "X > 1",
                                    "1 < 2",
                                    "0 > -1",
                                    "|-1|> 0"
                                ],
                                "correctAnswerIndex": 0
                            },
                            {
                                "questionText": "Choose Valid Syntax",
                                "options": [
                                    "2 / 0",
                                    "2 = 2",
                                    "2 == 2",
                                    "2 * 2 == 4"
                                ],
                                "correctAnswerIndex": 2
                            },
                            {
                                "questionText": "Pattern [././--] = 7 , [././ --] = 8, [././ ---]= ....?",
                                "options": [
                                    "8",
                                    "9",
                                    "10",
                                    "6"
                                ],
                                "correctAnswerIndex": 2
                            }
                        ]
                    }
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "courseId": "114",
            "title": "Control",
            "description": "",
            "instructorId": "7777",
            "status": "REJECTED",
            "lessons": [
            ]
        }
    ]
}